Columbia Pictures stills and key books LSC.2213
UCLA Library Special Collections
Columbia Pictures stills and key books
1933-1989
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.2213
253.2 linear feet (578 boxes, 2 record cartons)
Columbia Pictures history can be traced back to 1918 when brothers Harry and Jack Cohn formed a partnership with their associate Joe Brandt, to produce low-budget short films and featurettes; the three were former employees of Carl Laemmle. They called the company CBC Film Sales (Cohn-Brandt-Cohn). Incorporated in 1924, CBC became Columbia Pictures Corporation; films were created on Hollywood's Poverty Row, an area housing small production companies that churned out a large volume of low-budget westerns and B pictures. Columbia developed into to a major Hollywood studio by the 1930s due in part to the leadership of Harry Cohn and the talent of director Frank Capra. Capra contributed to a number of "firsts" for the studio including Columbia's first Academy Award for Best Picture of 1934 for It Happened One Night.
Conditions Governing Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance through our electronic paging system using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Columbia Pictures.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9974846473606533
Biography/History
Columbia Pictures history can be traced back to 1918 when brothers Harry and Jack Cohn formed a partnership with their associate Joe Brandt, to produce low-budget short films and featurettes; the three were former employees of Carl Laemmle. They called the company CBC Film Sales (Cohn-Brandt-Cohn). Incorporated in 1924, CBC became Columbia Pictures Corporation; films were created on Hollywood's Poverty Row, an area housing small production companies that churned out a large volume of low-budget westerns and B pictures. Columbia developed into to a major Hollywood studio by the 1930s due in part to the leadership of Harry Cohn and the talent of director Frank Capra. Capra contributed to a number of "firsts" for the studio including Columbia's first Academy Award for Best Picture of 1934 for It Happened One Night.
During the 1930's and 40's, the Cohn brothers expanded the studio by purchasing additional property in Burbank to use as a back lot for location filming. Additionally, in the late-1940s, Columbia Pictures was one of the first studios to venture into the television business with the formation of Screen Gems, later named Columbia Pictures Television, then Columbia TriStar Television. The late 1950's saw the deaths of both Cohn brothers and the end of an era at Columbia.
In 1968, the company reorganized changing it corporate title from Columbia Pictures Corporation to Columbia Pictures Industries with Columbia Pictures and Screen Gems as its major divisions. Financial difficulties in the 1970s lead the company to bankruptcy and a new management lead by Alan Hirschfield and David Begelman. Begelman was later replaced by Frank Price; Price was succeeded by David Puttnam, replaced one year later by Dawn Steel. The In 1982, Columbia was purchased by The Coca-Cola Company. By 1989, Sony Corporation purchased Columbia Pictures Corporation from The Coca-Cola Company, forming Sony Pictures Entertainment. The company relocated to the former Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer lot in Culver City, California and was renamed Sony Pictures Studios.
Among the films that contributed to the success of Columbia Pictures between the 1940s and 1980s were: The Jolson Story (1947), All the Kings Men (1949, Academy Award for Best Picture), The Bridge on the River Kwai (1957, Academy Award for Best Picture), Born Yesterday (1950), Bye Bye Birdie (1963), Close Encounters of the Third Kind (1977), Dr. Strangelove (1964), Easy Rider (1969), From Here to Eternity (1953), Funny Girl (1968), Ghostbusters (1984), Kramer Vs. Kramer (1979, Academy Award for Best Picture), Lawrence of Arabia (1962, Academy Award for Best Picture), A Man for All Seasons (1966, Academy Award for Best Picture), Midnight Express (1978), Oliver! (1968, Academy Award for Best Picture), On the Waterfront (1954), Shampoo (1975), Stripes (1981), Taxi Driver (1976), To Sir with Love (1967), Tootsie (1982), and The Way We Were (1973).
Sources: Katz Film Encyclopedia, 1979; UCLA Film and Television Archive.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of Columbia Pictures' stills and key books, documenting produced films from the mid-1930s to late-1980s. Included are prints, proof sheets, negatives, slides, and transparencies that depict scenes, as well as off-camera photographs showing various aspects of production filming, and publicity portraits. Among the 500-plus films represented in the collection are The Bridge on the River Kwai (1957), Bob & Carol & Ted & Alice (1969), Born Free (1966), Born Yesterday (1950), Butterflies Are Free (1972), Bye Bye Birdie (1963), The Cardinal (1963), Cat Ballou (1965), Dr. Strangelove (1964), Easy Rider (1969), From Here to Eternity (1953), Funny Girl (1968), Georgy Girl (1966), Guess Who's Coming to Dinner? (1967), The Guns of Navarone (1961), I Never Sang for My Father (1970), King Rat (1965), A Man for All Seasons, Oliver! (1968), Picnic (1955), On the Waterfront (1954), Ship of Fools (1965), Stripes (1981), Taxi Driver (1976), and The Way We Were (1973), among many others.
Organization and Arrangement
The collections is arranged alphabetically by project titles, which may be working title, alternate title, or release title, and for a small amount of files by person's name.
Motion picture studios--California--Los Angeles--Archives.
- Series 1. Large files
  Scope and Contents
  Files in this series typically each contain thirty or more images.
  - Actors, (1966) (Box 92)
    Todd Armstrong, Joby Baker, Harrison Ford, James Fox, Joe Gallison, Rian Garrick, Chuck Henerson, Duke Hobbie, Tom Nardini, and Clint Ritchie.
  - Actresses, (1960) (Box 88)
    Senta Berger, Carol Douglas, Kathryn Grant, Janet Landgard, Margie Regan, Camilla Sparv, Stella Stevens, and Nina Wayne.
  - $ [Dollars], (1971) (Box 40)
  - $ [Dollars], (1971) (Box 457)
  - 10 RILLINGTON PLACE, (1971) (Box 383)
  - 10 RILLINGTON PLACE, (1971) (Box 535)
  - 1001 ARABIAN NIGHTS, (1959) (Box 122)
  - 1001 ARABIAN NIGHTS, (1959) (Box 265)
  - 12 HOURS TO KILL, (1960) (Box 22)
  - 12 TO THE MOON, (1960) (Box 83)
  - 12 TO THE MOON, (1960) (Box 274)
  - 13 FIGHTING MEN, (1960) (Box 32)
  - 13 FRIGHTENED GIRLS, (1963) (Box 93)
  - 13 FRIGHTENED GIRLS, (1963) (Box 446)
  - 13 FRIGHTENED GIRLS, (1963) (Box 447)
  - 13 GHOSTS, (1960) (Box 279)
  - 13 WEST STREET, (1962) (Box 271)
  - 13 WEST STREET, (1962) (Box 272)
  - 13 WEST STREET (folder titled 13 E STREET), (1962) (Box 91)
  - 1776, (1972) (Box 62)
  - 1776, (1972) (Box 376)
  - 1776, (1972) (Box 519)
  - 1776, (1972) (Box 553)
  - 2ND TIME AROUND, THE, (1961) (Box 168)
  - 3 WORLDS OF GULLIVER, THE, (1960) (Box 574)
  - 3 WORLDS OF GULLIVER, THE (folder titled GULLIVER'S TRAVEL), (1960) (Box 107)
  - 3:10 TO YUMA, (1957) (Box 117)
  - 3:10 TO YUMA, (1957) (Box 269)
  - 30 IS A DANGEROUS AGE, CYNTHIA, (1968) (Box 76)
  - 30 IS A DANGEROUS AGE, CYNTHIA, (1968) (Box 212)
  - 30-FOOT BRIDE OF CANDY ROCK (folder titled HIS 30-FOOT BRIDE), (1959) (Box 108)
  - 39 STEPS, THE, (1959) (Box 23)
  - 39 STEPS, THE, (1959) (Box 34)
  - 40 CARATS, (1973) (Box 116)
  - AARON LOVES ANGELA, (1975) (Box 414)
  - AARON LOVES ANGELA, (1975) (Box 461)
  - AARON LOVES ANGELA, (1975) (Box 470)
    Slides only.
  - AARON LOVES ANGELA, (1975) (Box 487)
  - ADVISE & CONSENT, (1962) (Box 2)
  - ADVISE & CONSENT, (1962) (Box 448)
  - AGE OF CONSENT, (1969) (Box 61)
  - AGE OF CONSENT, (1969) (Box 333)
  - AGE OF CONSENT, (1969) (Box 534)
  - AGONY AND THE ECSTACY, THE, (1965) (Box 38)
  - AGONY AND THE ECSTACY, THE, (1965) (Box 39)
  - ALASKA PASSAGE, (1959) (Box 34)
  - ALL THE RIGHT MOVES, (1983) (Box 479)
  - ALL THE YOUNG MEN, (1960) (Box 264)
  - ALL THE YOUNG MEN, (1960) (Box 265)
  - ALVAREZ KELLY, (1966) (Box 49)
  - ALVAREZ KELLY, (1966) (Box 312)
  - ALVAREZ KELLY, (1966) (Box 313)
  - AMBUSHERS, THE, (1967) (Box 109)
  - AMBUSHERS, THE, (1967) (Box 411)
  - AMBUSHERS, THE, (1967) (Box 412)
  - AMBUSHERS, THE, (1967) (Box 520)
  - ANATOMY OF A MURDER, (1959) (Box 65)
  - ANATOMY OF A MURDER, (1959) (Box 234)
  - ANATOMY OF A MURDER, (1959) (Box 384)
  - ANATOMY OF A MURDER, (1959) (Box 516)
  - ANDERSON TAPES, THE, (1971) (Box 58)
  - ANDERSON TAPES, THE, (1971) (Box 333)
  - ANDERSON TAPES, THE, (1971) (Box 542)
  - Ando, Eiko, (1958) (Box 26)
  - ANZIO (US release title), (1968) (Box 86)
  - ANZIO (US release title), (1968) (Box 444)
  - ANZIO (US release title), (1968) (Box 445)
  - APACHE TERRITORY, (1958) (Box 140)
  - ARIZONA RAIDERS, THE, (1965) (Box 137)
  - ARIZONA RAIDERS, THE, (1965) (Box 319)
  - ARRUZA, (1972) (Box 334)
  - ASSIGNMENT K, (1968) (Box 108)
  - ASSIGNMENT K, (1968) (Box 438)
  - BABETTE GOES TO WAR (US release title), (1959) (Box 79)
  - BABETTE GOES TO WAR (US release title), (1959) (Box 257)
  - BABY, THE RAIN MUST FALL (folder titled THE TRAVELING LADY), (1965) (Box 72)
  - BABY, THE RAIN MUST FALL (folder titled THE TRAVELING LADY), (1965) (Box 277)
  - BACHELOR FLAT, (1962) (Box 162)
  - BANDIT OF ZHOBE, THE, (1959) (Box 295)
  - BARABBAS, (1961) (Box 125)
  - BARABBAS, (1961) (Box 242)
  - BATTLE OF THE CORAL SEA, (1959) (Box 89)
  - BECAUSE THEY'RE YOUNG, (1960) (Box 140)
  - BED AND BOARD (US release title), (1970) (Box 45)
  - BED AND BOARD (US release title), (1970) (Box 345)
  - BEDFORD INCIDENT, THE, (1965) (Box 60)
  - BEDFORD INCIDENT, THE, (1965) (Box 418)
  - BEFORE WINTER COMES, (1969) (Box 40)
  - BEFORE WINTER COMES, (1969) (Box 320)
  - BEFORE WINTER COMES, (1969) (Box 546)
  - BEHOLD A PALE HORSE, (1964) (Box 143)
  - BEHOLD A PALE HORSE, (1964) (Box 466)
  - BEHOLD A PALE HORSE, (1964) (Box 467)
  - BELLE SOMMERS, (1962) (Box 136)
  - BELLE SOMMERS, (1962) (Box 225)
  - BELOVED INFIDEL, (1959) (Box 28)
  - BELOVED INFIDEL, (1959) (Box 28)
  - BELOVED INFIDEL, (1959) (Box 161)
  - BERSERK!, (1967) (Box 108)
  - BERSERK!, (1967) (Box 445)
  - BEST OF ENEMIES, THE, (1962) (Box 140)
  - BEST OF ENEMIES, THE, (1962) (Box 302)
  - BIG GUNDOWN, THE (US release title), (1966) (Box 55)
  - BIG GUNDOWN, THE (US release title), (1966) (Box 334)
  - BIG GUNDOWN, THE (US release title), (1966) (Box 555)
  - BIG MOUTH, THE, (1967) (Box 132)
  - BIG MOUTH, THE, (1967) (Box 247)
  - BIG SHOW, THE, (1961) (Box 163)
  - BIRDS DO IT, BEES DO IT, (1961) (Box 133)
  - BIRDS DO IT, BEES DO IT, (1961) (Box 314)
  - BIRDS DO IT, BEES DO IT, (1961) (Box 461)
  - BIRDS DO IT, BEES DO IT, (1961) (Box 465)
  - BIRDS DO IT, BEES DO IT, (1971) (Box 469)
  - BIRDS DO IT, BEES DO IT, (1961) (Box 476)
  - BITE THE BULLET, (1975) (Box 464)
  - BITE THE BULLET, (1975) (Box 464)
  - BITE THE BULLET, (1975) (Box 476)
  - BITE THE BULLET, (1975) (Box 568)
  - BLACK BIRD, THE, (1972) (Box 209)
  - BLACK BIRD, THE, (1972) (Box 210)
  - BLACK BIRD, THE, (1972) (Box 211)
  - BLACK BIRD, THE, (1972) (Box 472)
  - BLACK BIRD, THE, (1975) (Box 485)
    Negatives only.
  - BLACK BIRD, THE, (1975) (Box 565)
  - BLACK GUNN, (1972) (Box 65)
  - BLACK GUNN, (1972) (Box 335)
    Negatives and slides only.
  - Blair, June, (1958) (Box 21)
  - BLAME IT ON RIO, (1984) (Box 481)
  - BLESS THE BEASTS AND CHILDREN, (1971) (Box 53)
  - BLESS THE BEASTS AND CHILDREN, (1971) (Box 334)
  - BLESS THE BEASTS AND CHILDREN, (1971) (Box 550)
  - BLUE DENIM, (1959) (Box 22)
  - BLUE DENIM, (1959) (Box 162)
  - BLUE DENIM, (1959) (Box 163)
  - BLUE DENIM, (1959) (Box 164)
  - BOB & CAROL & TED & ALICE, (1969) (Box 44)
  - BOB & CAROL & TED & ALICE, (1969) (Box 335)
  - BOB & CAROL & TED & ALICE, (1969) (Box 336)
  - BOBBIKINS, (1959) (Box 33)
  - BONJOUR TRISTESSE, (1958) (Box 73)
  - BONJOUR TRISTESSE, (1958) (Box 228)
  - Boone, Richard, (1959) (Box 22)
  - BORN FREE, (1966) (Box 115)
  - BORN YESTERDAY, (1950) (Box 245)
  - BORN YESTERDAY, (1950) (Box 246)
  - BREAKING AWAY, (1979) (Box 564)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 399)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 400)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 471)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 484)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 507)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 508)
  - BREAKOUT, (1975) (Box 567)
  - BRIDGE ON THE RIVER KWAI, (1957) (Box 83)
  - BRIDGE ON THE RIVER KWAI, (1957) (Box 428)
  - BRIEF SEASON (US release title), (1969) (Box 46)
  - BRIEF SEASON (US release title), (1969) (Box 334)
  - Britt, May, (1959) (Box 22)
  - BROTHER JOHN, (1971) (Box 46)
  - BROTHER JOHN, (1971) (Box 335)
  - BROTHER JOHN, (1971) (Box 518)
  - BROTHERHOOD OF SATAN, THE, (1971) (Box 55)
  - BROTHERHOOD OF SATAN, THE, (1971) (Box 179)
  - BROTHERHOOD OF SATAN, THE, (1971) (Box 549)
  - BUCHANAN RIDES ALONE (listed as NAME'S BUCHANAN), (1958) (Box 73)
  - BUCHANAN RIDES ALONE, (1958) (Box 192)
  - BUCK AND THE PREACHER, (1972) (Box 47)
  - BUCK AND THE PREACHER, (1972) (Box 180)
  - BUCK AND THE PREACHER, (1972) (Box 542)
  - BUDDY SYSTEM, THE, (1984) (Box 482)
  - BUNNY LAKE IS MISSING, (1965) (Box 128)
  - BUNNY LAKE IS MISSING, (1965) (Box 208)
  - BURGLARS, THE (US release title), (1971) (Box 109)
  - BURGLARS, THE (US release title), (1971) (Box 336)
  - BURGLARS, THE (US release title), (1971) (Box 549)
  - Busch, Judy, (1956) (Box 23)
  - BUTTERCUP CHAIN, THE, (1970) (Box 54)
  - BUTTERCUP CHAIN, THE, (1970) (Box 201)
  - BUTTERCUP CHAIN, THE, (1970) (Box 542)
  - BUTTERFLIES ARE FREE, (1972) (Box 114)
  - BUTTERFLIES ARE FREE, (1972) (Box 337)
  - BUTTERFLIES ARE FREE, (1972) (Box 338)
  - BYE BYE BIRDIE, (1963) (Box 43)
  - BYE BYE BIRDIE, (1963) (Box 211)
  - BYE BYE BIRDIE, (1963) (Box 494)
  - BYE BYE BIRDIE, (1963) (Box 506)
  - CACTUS FLOWER, (1969) (Box 70)
  - CACTUS FLOWER, (1969) (Box 339)
  - CACTUS FLOWER, (1969) (Box 340)
  - CAINE MUTINY, THE, (1954) (Box 74)
  - CALIFORNIA SPLIT, (1974) (Box 395)
  - CALIFORNIA SPLIT, (1974) (Box 499)
  - CALIFORNIA SPLIT, (1974) (Box 517)
  - CALIFORNIA SPLIT, (1974) (Box 566)
    Slides and negatives only.
  - Callan, Michael (portraits, family, and art)), (1959) (Box 61)
  - CALYPSO HEATWAVE, (1957) (Box 129)
  - CAMP ON BLOOD ISLAND, THE, (1958) (Box 127)
  - CAPTAIN FROM CASTILLE, (1947) (Box 120)
  - CAPTAIN FROM CASTILLE, (1947) (Box 121)
  - CAPTAIN FROM CASTILLE, (1947) (Box 125)
  - CAPTAIN'S TABLE, THE, (1959) (Box 37)
  - CAPTAIN'S TABLE, THE, (1959) (Box 87)
  - CAPTAIN'S TABLE, THE, (1959) (Box 114)
  - CARDINAL, THE, (1963) (Box 75)
  - CARDINAL, THE, (1963) (Box 454)
  - CARDINAL, THE, (1963) (Box 455)
  - CASE AGAINST BROOKLYN, THE, (1958) (Box 80)
  - CASINO ROYALE, (1967) (Box 42)
  - CASINO ROYALE, (1967) (Box 451)
  - CASTLE KEEP, (1969) (Box 136)
  - CASTLE KEEP, (1969) (Box 205)
  - CAT BALLOU, (1965) (Box 64)
  - CAT BALLOU, (1965) (Box 383)
  - CAT BALLOU, (1965) (Box 497)
  - CAT BALLOU, (1965) (Box 498)
  - CERTAIN SMILE, A, (1958) (Box 152)
  - CHANGE OF SEASONS, A, (1980) (Box 557)
  - CHANGE OF SEASONS, A, (1980) (Box 559)
  - CHASE, THE, (1966) (Box 85)
  - CHASE, THE, (1966) (Box 316)
  - CHASE, THE, (1966) (Box 317)
  - CHINA IS NEAR (US release title), (1967) (Box 135)
  - CHINA IS NEAR (US release title), (1967) (Box 314)
  - CHINESE CONNECTION, THE, (1972) (Box 476)
  - CHLOE IN THE AFTERNOON (US release title; folder titled LOVE IN THE AFTERNOON), (1972) (Box 43)
  - CHLOE IN THE AFTERNOON (US release title; folder titled LOVE IN THE AFTERNOON), (1972) (Box 333)
  - CHLOE IN THE AFTERNOON (US release title; folder titled LOVE IN THE AFTERNOON), (1972) (Box 535)
  - CHOSEN SURVIVORS, (1974) (Box 401)
  - CHOSEN SURVIVORS, (1974) (Box 461)
  - CHOSEN SURVIVORS, (1974) (Box 496)
  - CISCO PIKE (folder titled DEALER), (1972) (Box 44)
  - CISCO PIKE (folder titled DEALER), (1972) (Box 341)
  - CITY OF FEAR, (1959) (Box 108)
  - CLAIRE'S KNEE (US release title), (1970) (Box 62)
  - CLAIRE'S KNEE (US release title), (1970) (Box 350)
  - CLAIRE'S KNEE (US release title), (1970) (Box 523)
  - CODE 7 - VICTIM 5, (1964) (Box 315)
  - COLLECTOR, THE, (1965) (Box 329)
  - COMANCHE STATION, (1960) (Box 52)
  - COMIC, THE, (1969) (Box 44)
  - COMIC, THE, (1969) (Box 182)
  - COMIC, THE, (1969) (Box 183)
  - COMIC, THE, (1969) (Box 184)
  - COMANCHEROS, THE, (1961) (Box 153)
  - CONFESSIONS OF A POP PERFORMER, (1975) (Box 407)
  - CONFESSIONS OF A POP PERFORMER, (1975) (Box 475)
  - CONFESSIONS OF A POP PERFORMER, (1975) (Box 476)
  - CONGO VIVO, (1962) (Box 53)
  - Connor, Tami / PEYTON PLACE, (1957) (Box 20)
  - Contract players, (1956) (Box 100)
  - Contract players, (1959) (Box 133)
  - Corbett, Glenn, (1959) (Box 94)
  - CORRUPTION, (1968) (Box 239)
  - COURAGE OF BLACK BEAUTY, (1957) (Box 114)
  - COWBOY, (1958) (Box 58)
  - COWBOY, (1958) (Box 80)
  - COWBOY, (1958) (Box 229)
  - COWBOY, (1958) (Box 230)
  - CRAZY JOE, (1974) (Box 342)
  - CREATURES THE WORLD FORGO, (1971) (Box 105)
  - CREATURES THE WORLD FORGOT, (1971) (Box 342)
  - CREEPING FLESH, THE, (1973) (Box 88)
  - CREEPING FLESH, THE, (1973) (Box 462)
  - CREEPING FLESH, THE, (1973) (Box 462)
  - CRIMSON BLADE, THE (folder listed as THE SCARLET BLADE), (1963) (Box 232)
  - CRIMSON KIMONO, THE, (1959) (Box 98)
  - CRIMSON KIMONO, THE, (1959) (Box 266)
  - CROMWELL, (1970) (Box 5)
  - CROMWELL, (1970) (Box 139)
  - CROMWELL, (1970) (Box 342)
  - CRY FOR HAPPY, (1961) (Box 106)
  - CRY FOR HAPPY, (1961) (Box 252)
  - CRY FOR HAPPY, (1961) (Box 253)
  - CURSE OF THE MUMMY'S TOMB, (1964) (Box 319)
  - DANDY IN ASPIC, A, (1968) (Box 10)
  - DANDY IN ASPIC, A, (1968) (Box 343)
  - Darren, James, (1959) (Box 70)
  - DAY IN THE DEATH OF JOE EGG, A, (1972) (Box 44)
  - DAY IN THE DEATH OF JOE EGG, A, (1972) (Box 142)
  - DAY IN THE DEATH OF JOE EGG, A, (1972) (Box 343)
  - DEAD HEAT ON A MERRY-GO-ROUND, (1966) (Box 136)
  - DEAD HEAT ON A MERRY-GO-ROUND, (1966) (Box 231)
  - DEADLY AFFAIR, THE, (1966) (Box 17)
  - DEADLY AFFAIR, THE, (1966) (Box 393)
  - DEADLY AFFAIR, THE, (1966) (Box 504)
  - DEATH WISH, (1974) (Box 142)
  - DEATH WISH (folder titled VIGILANTE IN THE STREET), (1974) (Box 467)
  - DEATH WISH (folder titled VIGILANTE IN THE STREET), (1974) (Box 568)
  - DECISION AT SUNDOWN, (1957) (Box 122)
  - DESIRE IN THE DUST, (1960) (Box 22)
  - DESPERADOS, THE, (1969) (Box 48)
  - DEVIL-SHIP PIRATES, THE, (1964) (Box 128)
  - DEVIL-SHIP PIRATES, THE, (1964) (Box 215)
  - DIAMOND HEAD, (1963) (Box 84)
    Negatives and transparencies only.
  - DIAMOND HEAD, (1963) (Box 259)
  - DIAMOND HEAD, (1963) (Box 260)
  - DIARY OF ANNE FRANK, THE, (1959) (Box 6)
  - DIARY OF ANNE FRANK, THE, (1959) (Box 21)
  - DIRTY DOZEN, THE, (1967) (Box 119)
  - DIRTY LITTLE BILLY, (1972) (Box 101)
  - DIRTY LITTLE BILLY, (1972) (Box 345)
  - DIRTY LITTLE BILLY, (1972) (Box 546)
  - DIRTY LITTLE BILLY, (1972) (Box 554)
  - DIVORCE, AMERICAN STYLE, (1967) (Box 17)
  - DIVORCE, AMERICAN STYLE, (1967) (Box 325)
  - DIVORCE, AMERICAN STYLE, (1967) (Box 327)
  - DIVORCE, AMERICAN STYLE, (1967) (Box 513)
  - DIVORCE, AMERICAN STYLE, (1967) (Box 514)
  - DOCTOR'S WIVES, (1971) (Box 345)
  - DOCTORS' WIVES, (1971) (Box 46)
  - DOMINO KID (folder titled DOMINO), (1957) (Box 66)
  - DON'T KNOCK THE TWIST (folder titled THE BRISTOL STOMP), (1962) (Box 70)
  - DON'T KNOCK THE TWIST (folder titled THE BRISTOL STOMP), (1962) (Box 315)
  - DON'T RAISE THE BRIDGE, LOWER THE RIVER, (1967) (Box 20)
  - DON'T RAISE THE BRIDGE, LOWER THE RIVER, (1967) (Box 143)
  - DON'T RAISE THE BRIDGE, LOWER THE RIVER, (1967) (Box 331)
  - DON'T RAISE THE BRIDGE, LOWER THE RIVER, (1967) (Box 332)
  - DON'T RAISE THE BRIDGE, LOWER THE RIVER, (1967) (Box 333)
  - DORA DOLL, (1958) (Box 22)
  - DR. FAUSTUS, (1967) (Box 61)
  - DR. FAUSTUS, (1967) (Box 419)
  - DR. STRANGELOVE, (1964) (Box 19)
  - DR. STRANGELOVE, (1964) (Box 416)
  - DRIVE, HE SAID, (1971) (Box 49)
  - DRIVE, HE SAID, (1971) (Box 345)
  - DUFFY, (1968) (Box 131)
  - DUFFY, (1968) (Box 223)
  - DUFFY, (1968) (Box 223)
  - DUFFY, (1968) (Box 224)
  - EAST OF SUDAN, (1964) (Box 136)
  - EAST OF SUDAN, (1964) (Box 254)
  - EASY RIDER, (1969) (Box 422)
  - EASY RIDER, (1969) (Box 576)
  - EDDY DUCHIN STORY, THE, (1956) (Box 78)
  - EDGE OF ETERNITY (folder titled SATAN'S BUCKET), (1959) (Box 87)
  - EDGE OF ETERNITY (folder titled SATAN'S BUCKET), (1959) (Box 225)
  - EDGE OF ETERNITY (folder titled SATAN'S BUCKET), (1959) (Box 226)
  - ENEMY GENERAL, THE, (1960) (Box 53)
  - ENEMY GENERAL, THE, (1960) (Box 234)
  - ENTER LAUGHING, (1967) (Box 60)
  - ENTER LAUGHING, (1967) (Box 145)
  - ENTER LAUGHING, (1967) (Box 447)
  - ESTHER AND THE KING, (1960) (Box 34)
  - EVERYTHING'S DUCKY, (1961) (Box 47)
  - EXECUTIONER, THE, (1970) (Box 8)
  - EXECUTIONER, THE, (1970) (Box 345)
  - EXPERIMENT IN TERROR, (1962) (Box 2)
  - EXPERIMENT IN TERROR, (1962) (Box 80)
  - EXPERIMENT IN TERROR, (1962) (Box 90)
  - EXPERIMENT IN TERROR, (1962) (Box 410)
  - EXPERIMENT IN TERROR, (1962) (Box 523)
  - FACE OF A FUGITIVE, (1959) (Box 88)
  - FANATIC (folder titled DIE! DIE! MY DARLING), (1965) (Box 178)
  - FANATIC (folder titled DIE! DIE! MY DARLING), (1965) (Box 241)
  - FAREWELL TO ARMS, A, (1957) (Box 28)
  - FAREWELL TO ARMS, A, (1957) (Box 28)
  - FAREWELL TO ARMS, A, (1957) (Box 150)
  - FAT CITY, (1972) (Box 19)
  - FAT CITY, (1972) (Box 346)
  - FERRY TO HONG KONG, (1959) (Box 24)
  - FIERCEST HEART, THE, (1961) (Box 26)
  - FIERCEST HEART, THE, (1961) (Box 149)
  - FINAL CONFLICT, THE, (1981) (Box 556)
  - FINAL CONFLICT, THE, (1981) (Box 557)
  - FINEST HOURS, (1964) (Box 227)
  - FIRE DOWN BELOW, (1957) (Box 115)
  - FIRST MEN IN THE MOON, (1964) (Box 132)
  - FIRST MEN IN THE MOON, (1964) (Box 245)
  - FISTS OF FURY, (1971) (Box 476)
  - FIVE EASY PIECES, (1970) (Box 144)
  - FIVE EASY PIECES, (1970) (Box 245)
  - FIVE FINGER EXERCISE, (1962) (Box 143)
  - FIVE FINGER EXERCISE, (1962) (Box 253)
  - FIVE FINGER EXERCISE, (1962) (Box 254)
  - FIVE GOLDEN HOURS, (1961) (Box 126)
  - FIVE GOLDEN HOURS, (1961) (Box 255)
  - FIVE GOLDEN HOURS, (1961) (Box 256)
  - FLIGHT OF THE DOVES, (1971) (Box 4)
  - FLIGHT OF THE DOVES, (1971) (Box 346)
  - FLY, THE, (1958) (Box 152)
  - FLYING FONTAINES, THE, (1959) (Box 122)
  - FLYING FONTAINES, THE, (1959) (Box 241)
  - FLYING FONTAINES, THE, (1959) (Box 242)
  - FOOL'S PARADE, (1971) (Box 124)
  - FOOL'S PARADE, (1971) (Box 347)
  - FOR PETE'S SAKE, (1974) (Box 347)
  - FOR PETE'S SAKE, (1974) (Box 467)
  - FOR SINGLES ONLY, (1968) (Box 235)
  - FOR SINGLES ONLY, (1968) (Box 236)
  - FOR THE LOVE OF MIKE, (1960) (Box 26)
  - FORBIDDEN ISLAND, (1959) (Box 47)
  - FORTY CARATS, (1973) (Box 348)
  - FORTY CARATS, (1973) (Box 349)
  - FORTY GUNS TO APACHE PASS, (1967) (Box 134)
  - FORTY GUNS TO APACHE PASS, (1967) (Box 250)
  - FORTY GUNS TO APACHE PASS, (1967) (Box 251)
  - FORTY GUNS TO APACHE PASS, (1967) (Box 252)
  - FRAGMENT OF FEAR, (1970) (Box 129)
  - FRAGMENT OF FEAR, (1970) (Box 350)
  - FRANCIS OF ASSISSI, (1961) (Box 25)
  - FRANCIS OF ASSISSI, (1961) (Box 153)
  - FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (1953) (Box 12)
  - FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (1953) (Box 18)
  - FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (1953) (Box 50)
  - FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (1953) (Box 390)
  - FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (1953) (Box 506)
  - FROM THE TERRACE, (1960) (Box 150)
  - FRONTIER HELLCAT, (1964) (Box 255)
  - FUNNY GIRL, (1968) (Box 328)
  - FUNNY GIRL, (1968) (Box 329)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 395)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 396)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 397)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 398)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 399)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 467)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 473)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 474)
    Slides and transparencies only.
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 486)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 517)
  - FUNNY LADY, (1975) (Box 565)
  - GAME IS OVER, THE (US release title), (1966) (Box 132)